[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：我们获得了新版本的JavaScript，该版本已获得批准
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We've got a new version of JavaScript that was approved by
六个月前的大会
the general assembly six months ago and
它的许多功能现在已经在浏览器中了。
many of the features of it are already in browsers now.
他们中的一些人会晚些时候来，所以这是一个很好的时间
And some of them will be coming in later and so this is a good time to
看看新语言里有什么，我们在里面有什么好东西吗？
look at what's in the new language, did we get any good stuff in it?
答案是肯定的，我们确实有很多好东西在里面。
And the answer is yes we've got actually lot of good stuff in it.
因此，我最喜欢的语言新功能中最合适的尾部调用。
So my number one most favorite new feature of the language proper tail calls.
因此编译器会将其转换为跳转而不是调用返回，
So compiler will turn that into a jump instead of a call return,
所以它会跑得更快一点。
so it'll go a little faster.
在到达那里时占用较少的内存，
Take less memory in getting there,
它支持其他编程模式中的延续传递风格，这很棒。
it enables continuation passing style in other modes of programming, it's great.
这是我最喜欢的JavaScript特性
So that's my most favorite feature with this JavaScript finally
成为一种真正的函数式编程语言，这很棒。
becomes a real functional programming language, which is great.
我第二个最喜欢的新特性，省略号运算符，我们已经
My second most favorite new feature, the ellipsis operator which we've
昨天又谈了相当多，是咖喱函数的两个版本。
talk about quite a bit yesterday again is two versions of the curry function.
有一个和那个，他们都做同样的事情。
There is that one and that one, they both do the same thing.
这一次是不可原谅的
This one's inexcusable,
这个实际上非常好，所以它将是一件好事。
this one's actually pretty nice so that it's going to be a good thing.
我们现在有了语言中的模块，不幸的是，我们得到的模块系统是
We've got modules in the language now unfortunately the module system we got is
太复杂了。
way too complex.
但是它是有效的，所以有一个模块系统的子集是足够的。
But it works, so there's a subset of the module system which is adequate.
如果你只是想说这里有一些东西，我要出口这个东西。
Which if you just wanna say here's some stuff, I'm gonna export this thing.
这就是你如何使用它，这就是它所需要的，它可以做到这一点。
That's how you use it and that's all it needs to be, and it can do that.
所以这很好，比要求的要好得多，或者
So that's good, that's much better than requires, or
任何其他模块加载器。
any of the other module loaders.
我们已经让康斯特进来了，这本身并不是什么大不了的事。
We've got let in const, which by themselves are not that big a deal.
除了它们对Java程序员来说不那么令人困惑之外。
Except they are less confusing to Java programmers.
所以最好不要让Java程序员感到困惑，所以我喜欢这样。
So it's good not to confuse the Java programmers, so I like that.
我对此感到困惑的一件事是我看到了很多
One thing I find confusing about this is that I've seen a lot
对于常量和冻结之间的区别感到困惑的开发人员。
of developers who are confused about the difference between const and freezing.
所以他们很惊讶你可以把一个可变的对象放在一个常量和
And so they're surprised that you can put a mutable object in a const and
仍然使对象发生变异。
still mutate that object.
所以变量的常量，冻结是
So constants for variables, freezing is for
价值观，只要记住这一点，这是相当容易的。
values, just remember that, it's pretty easy.
我们有解构，解构是你可以做的事情
We have Destructuring, destructuring is something you can do and
let和can语句，以及赋值语句中的语句。
let and can't statements, and also in assignment statements.
在那里我们可以创建新的变量和
Where we can create new variables and
同时从某个对象初始化它们。
initialize them from some object at the same time.
所以同样不是一个大的改变，不会让我们做我们以前做不到的事情，但是
So again not a big change, doesn't let us do anything we couldn't do before but
这是一种方便，是的。
it is a convenience, yeah.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：我想你说过冻结是为了价值观，你的意思是冻结是为了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I think you said freezing is for values, did you mean freezing is for
物品？
objects?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：对象是值。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Objects are values.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay, yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：理论上你可以冻结号码，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: In theory you could freeze numbers,
只是它们已经被冻结了，而且字符串已经被冻结了。
except they're already frozen, and strings are already frozen.
所以你不需要冷冻它们。
So you don't need to freeze those.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：一次跟进，除了嵌套对象之外，还有什么？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: One follow up, what apart about nested objects?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：它只冻结外部的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: It only freezes the outer one,
语言中没有深深的冻结。
there is no deep freeze in the language.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以你必须进行递归冻结。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So you have to do a recursive freeze.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：如果你关心这一点，你必须下降到语言和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: If you care about that, you have to descend into the language and
冻结每个级别。
freeze each level.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：然后我们有WeakMap，WeakMap是一个非常好的东西。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Then we have WeakMap, WeakMap is a really nice thing.
WeakMap的工作方式与对象的工作方式相同。
WeakMap works the way objects should work.
使用WeakMap，您可以获取任何JavaScript值并将其用作键，然后
With a WeakMap you can take any JavaScript value and use it as a key and then
将任何其他值与其关联，这是对象应该工作的方式。
associate any other value with it which is the way object should have worked.
而且它还有一个很好的属性，它不会为其路由密钥
And it also has a nice property that it does not route the keys for
垃圾收集的目的。
the purpose of garbage collecting.
因此，如果对象仍然存在的唯一位置是作为
So if the only place where an object still exists is as the key of a property in
一个WeakMap，它会被自动垃圾收集，这是辉煌的。
a WeakMap, it will get garbage collected automatically, which is brilliant.
这意味着我们可以编写一类应用程序
So that means there is a class of applications which we can write in
JavaScript现在使用了我们以前无法用这种语言编写的WeakMap，
JavaScript now using WeakMap that we could not write in the language before,
这真的很好。
which is really nice.
WeakMap最大的问题是它可能是有史以来在要素上使用的最糟糕的名称
The biggest problem with WeakMap is it has maybe the worst name ever put on a feature
编程语言的。
of a programming language.
因为谁想使用一个叫做WeakMap的东西，对吧？
Because who wants to use something called a WeakMap, right?
但实际上这真的是一件好事。
But it's actually a really good thing.
这只是一个非常糟糕的名字，我们有Megastring文字。
It's just a really bad name and we have Megastring literals.
我们有反勾号，我们现在可以用它来制作可以散布很多行的字面值，
We have the back tick which we can now use to make literals that can spam many lines,
这里有一个正则表达式的例子。
so here's are an example of a regular expression.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：这个特定的正则表达式匹配所有数字
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: This particular regular expression matches all of the number
是ES6的字面值。
literals that are an ES6.
你可以看到我为什么不喜欢正则表达式，因为
And you can see why I don't like regular expressions because
你不能从这个权利中得到任何意义。
you can't make any sense out of this right.
只是看看，这只是噪音，真的很难理解它是关于什么的。
Just looking at that, it's just noise it's really hard to understand what it's about.
所以我现在可以让事情变得更简单，我这里有一个函数，我们将
So I can make things all easier now, I've got a function here which we'll
调用正则表达式构造函数，以字符串形式传递它
call the regular expression constructor passing it in a string
但首先，它将删除该字符串中的所有空格。
but first it will remove all of the spaces from that string.
所以现在，我可以使用这些巨型文字之一
And so now, I can use one of these mega literals
写出包含所有空格的内容。
to write it out with all the whitespace in it.
其中有空格，
And with whitespace in it,
正则表达式并没有那么糟糕，我们得到了空格。
regular expressions aren't quite that bad, we get spaces between.
每个元素和我可以将它们排列起来
Each of the elements and I can line them up and
你可以看到发生了什么，所以我们现在有了二进制文字。
you can kind of see what's going on, so we now have binary literals.
您可以使用零B，后跟零和一，然后
You can have zero B followed by zeros and ones and
我们有一个字面上的，我仍然不确定这些。
we've got aka literal which I'm still not sure about those.
你得到一个0代表零，然后是八进制数字
You've got an 0 for a zero and then octal digits and
我们一直都有黑客和浮点数。
we've always had the hacks and the floating point.
所以这非常简洁，这是一种更好的读取正则表达式的方法。
So that's pretty neat, this is a much nicer way of reading regular expressions.
仍然有关于巨型文字的事情，我不喜欢。
There are still things about the mega literals and I don't like.
反勾号是我们得到的最小的运算符
That back tick is the smallest operator we've got and
它是用来支撑我们曾经拥有过的最大的建筑。
it's used to bracket the biggest structures we've ever had.
所以这里有可能会误读，所以
So there is potential for misreading here so
我们必须对此保持谨慎，但我认为这可能是一件好事。
we're gonna have to be cautious with this but I think this is probably a good thing.
同样正则表达式，如果您正在编写正则表达式
And again regulex, if you're writing regular expressions
即使有了空格，你还是想起诉Regulex。
even with the whitespace you still wanna be suing regulex.
所以我们有肥大的箭头功能，或者简称为放屁。
So we've got fat arrow functions or fart for short.
所以这里的动机，有人抱怨说
So the motivation here, there are people who are complaining that
使用函数时，您必须键入八个字母。
with function you have to type eight letters.
你必须F you N，我说这太多了，不能打字，我说好的
You have to F you N, and I said that's too much to type and I said well there
这些新东西现在叫做键盘后排，读起来太多了。
are these new things now called keyboard back rows, it's too much to read.
好的，所以我们添加了它们。
Okay, so we added them.
所以它是编写返回值的函数的缩写形式。
So it's a short form for writing a function that will return a value.
所以我们得到了参数列表，我们得到了名字，然后我们得到了放屁和
So we got the parameter list, we got name and then we got the fart and
然后我们得到它之后的返回值。
then we've got the return value after it.
因此，您不必编写函数和
So, you don't have to write function and
你不需要写回执，除非这会失败。
you don't have to write return except this will fail.
这看起来像是一个小的迷你构造函数，它将返回一个新的
This looks like it's a little mini constructor that's gonna return a new
反对吧？
object, right?
它将返回一个新的东西，其中的id是我们传递的名字，
It's gonna return a new thing where the id is whatever the name is that we passed,
这会失败的。
this is going to fail.
相反，它会给你一个返回undefined的函数，这是不好的。
Instead it's going to give you a function that returns undefined, which is not good.
这是因为语言中的句法歧义，
And it's because of a syntactic ambiguity in the language,
委员会在做这件事的时候意识到了这一点，
the committee was aware of this when they did it,
我们只是不断地添加新的坏部分，我们无法停止这样做。
we just keep adding new bad parts we can't stop doing it.
因此，正因为如此，我并不是一个很喜欢这些东西的人。
So because of that I'm not a big fan of these.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：所以它会编译，但不会运行。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So it will compile but it won't run.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：它将编译，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: It will compile,
它将运行，当您调用它时，它将返回undefined。
it will run, it will return undefined when you call it.
您将不会获得您试图构造的新对象。
You will not get the new object that you're trying to construct.
我们一直这样对自己
We keep doing this to ourselves,
继续这样对你，它实际上是如何工作的。
keep doing this to you, how that actually works.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：因为括号不明确？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Because the brackets are ambiguous?
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：是的，因为括号是模棱两可的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, because the brackets are ambiguous.
他们有很多方法可以消除它的歧义，
There are number of ways they could have disambiguated it,
但他们却决定制造它们。
but they decide instead to make them.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：几个快速[笑]，因为那不是你放进去的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: A couple quick [LAUGH] because that's not what you put inside
括号实际上不是函数的内容。
the brackets isn't really the contents of a function.
通常，函数将返回。
Typically, a function would return.
我很困惑，我把这个搞糊涂了。
I'm confused about, I'm confusing this.
我只是用另一种语言放屁。
I just fart with what we're using in another language.
在打字稿中，我认为，他们在打字稿中加入了var。
In TypeScript, I think, they put var in TypeScript.
我一直在用它，我用它来调用一个函数来做一些事情
I've been using it, I'm using it to call a function to do something
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：所以这将适用于
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So this will work for
很多其他目的，它失败的地方，
lots of other purposes, the place where it fails,
就好像你试图返回一个新的对象文字一样。
as if you're trying to return a new object literal.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：在这个X var X等于的另一边。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You would have on the other side of this X var X equals.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的，或者你传递这个更有可能将这个作为参数传递给另一个
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, or you pass this more likely pass this as an argument to another
函数，这是这些函数最常见的用法之一。
function That's one of the most common uses for these.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：所以不管怎样，继续，还有很多其他不好的部分
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So anyway moving on, and there are lots of other bad parts in
该语言也类似于产出率运算符的生成器，
the language too like generators with the yield operator,
我想那可能是个错误。
I think that was probably a mistake.
它增加了很多复杂性，但没有多少价值和某种程度上锁定了人们
It adds a lot of complexity and not much value and kind of locks people into
我认为我们应该从模式中进化出来
patterns which I think are things that we should be evolving away from and
不会被困在里面。
not getting trapped in.
还有很多我们还没有足够经验的其他新功能
A lot of the other new features we haven't had enough experience with
他们还不知道。
them yet to know.
如果他们是好的部分或坏的部分，但有一个部分
If they're going to be good parts or bad parts but there is one part
我相信这将是一个非常糟糕的部分，这就是课堂。
that I'm confident is going to be a very, very bad part and that is class.
这是ES6中请求最多的新功能，主要是由
This was the most requested new feature for ES6, it was mostly requested by
不得不转向JavaScript并对此感到不满的Java程序员。
Java programmers who were having to move into JavaScript and were unhappy about it.
然后说“请”你能把JavaScript转换成Java吗
And saying please can you turn JavaScript into Java so
我们不需要学习这种蹩脚的语言，所以我们就这么做了。
we don't have to learn this crappy language and so we did that.
只是我们实际上并没有添加我们所做的类
Except we didn't actually add class what we did
我们在已经存在的东西的原型之上添加了语法糖。
was we added syntactic sugar on top of the prototype of stuff that's already there.
所以当你进入边缘时，
So when you get down into the edges,
它不会像你期望的那样工作。
it's not going to work the way you expect it will.
但更糟糕的是，它让你陷入了古典的心态
But worse than that is it keeps you trapped in the mindset of the classical
模型，这意味着您永远不会学习使用功能模型。
model, which means you will never learn to use the functional model.
而且你也没有强大的类型系统
And also you don't have the strong type system
你需要它来处理课程。
that you need in order to deal with classes.
所以我很有信心
And so I'm pretty confident
那些将要使用课程的人会觉得自己是清白的。
that the people who are gonna be using classes are gonna feel vindicated.
它在标准中，我有权使用它。
It's in the standard, I have a right to use it.
这些都是好东西。
It's all that good stuff.
但他们永远学不会有效地使用这种语言。
But they will never learn to use the language effectively.
他们会回到自己的坟墓，永远不会知道自己有多悲惨。
They will go to their graves never knowing how miserable they were.